export const DATA = [
    {
        question: "how to clean teeth", 
        answer: "by brushing it!"
    }, 
    {
        question: "definition of red",
        answer: "a colour that is warm"
    }, 
    {
        question: "how is the tech industry like", 
        answer: "bad... "
    },
    {
        question: "teeth are green?", 
        answer: "some are purple"
    },
    {
        question: "why are trains important to the american society ", 
        answer: "trains are important due to the accessibility for transportation"
    },
]

export const DATA_TEMPLATE = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "", 
        answer: "",
    },
    {
        id: 2, 
        question: "", 
        answer: "",
    },
]

export const EXAMPLE_DATA = [
    {
        id: 1, 
        name: "TEST",
        owner: "Lucy", 
        data: [
            {
                id: 1,
                question: "test1",
                answer: "1"
            },
            {
                id: 2,
                question: "test2",
                answer: "2"
            },
            {
                id: 3,
                question: "test3",
                answer: "3"
            },
            {
                id: 4,
                question: "test4",
                answer: "4"
            },
            {
                id: 5,
                question: "test5",
                answer: "5"
            }
        ]
    }, 
    {
        id: 2, 
        name: "Biology", 
        owner: "Morryical", 
        data: [
            {
                id: 1,
                question: "what is a brain", 
                answer: "a brain is an organ "
            },
            {
                id: 2,
                question: "what about corn", 
                answer: "a corn is a vegetable"
            },
            {
                id: 3,
                question: "what do I need to succeed", 
                answer: "i'm not too sure, do your own research"
            },
            {
                id: 4,
                question: "why do i like pizza", 
                answer: "genetics"
            },
            {
                id: 5,
                question: "when was pene created", 
                answer: "1720"
            }
        ]
    }, 
    {
        id: 3, 
        name: "Chemistry", 
        owner: "Cheese and pie", 
        data: [
            {
                id: 1,
                question: "what is enthalpy", 
                answer: "measurement of energy in a thermodynamic system"
            },
            {
                id: 2,
                question: "what is CHOO3", 
                answer: "i don't know, glucose"
            },
            {
                id: 3,
                question: "what is therodynamics", 
                answer: "heat change in a system"
            },
            {
                id: 4,
                question: "what are the organic chemistry functional groups", 
                answer: "alkane, alkene, um there's a lot actually"
            },
            {
                id: 5,
                question: "what is titration", 
                answer: "method of determined the concetration of dissolved substance..."
            }
        ]
    }, 
    {
        id: 4, 
        name: "Phemistry", 
        owner: "Cheese and pie", 
        data: [
            {
                id: 1,
                question: "what is enthalpy", 
                answer: "measurement of energy in a thermodynamic system"
            },
            {
                id: 2,
                question: "what is CHOO3", 
                answer: "i don't know, glucose"
            },
            {
                id: 3,
                question: "what is therodynamics", 
                answer: "heat change in a system"
            },
            {
                id: 4,
                question: "what are the organic chemistry functional groups", 
                answer: "alkane, alkene, um there's a lot actually"
            },
            {
                id: 5,
                question: "what is titration", 
                answer: "method of determined the concetration of dissolved substance..."
            }
        ]
    }, 
]